Guide to the Edwin Clark Papers, 1798-1930 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Edwin Clark papers 1798-1930 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Clark, Edwin
4.8 linear feet Extent: 3,636 Items
Merchant, of Weldon (Halifax Co.), N.C. Records and business correspondence of a general merchant of Weldon, N.C., together with daybooks (1880-1918) and ledgers (1878). Also includes a letter from Washington and Lee University, Lexington, Va., concerning a son in college; and a letter from an instructor at Oak Ridge Military Institute, Guilford Co., N.C. (1917).
clarkedwin
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Edwin Clark Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 1938.
Collection Overview
Records and business correspondence of a general merchant of Weldon, N.C., together with daybooks (1880-1918) and ledgers (1878). Also includes a letter from Washington and Lee University, Lexington, Va., concerning a son in college; and a letter from an instructor at Oak Ridge Military Institute, Guilford Co., N.C. (1917).
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Washington and Lee University; Oak Ridge Military Institute (Guilford Co., N.C.).; Merchants -- North Carolina; Business records -- North Carolina; Education -- Southern States; Weldon (N.C.)--Commerce
Contents of Collection
- Records and Business Correspondence Series, 1798-1930 and undated (bulk 1878-1918), (11 boxes)
  - Papers, 1798-1897 (Box 1)
  - Papers, 1898-1904 (Box 2)
  - Papers, 1905-1908 (Box 3)
  - Papers, 1908-1909 (Box 4)
  - Papers, 1909-1910 (Box 5)
  - Papers, 1910-1911 (Box 6)
  - Papers, 1911-1912 (Box 7)
  - Papers, 1912-1913 (Box 8)
  - Papers, 1913-1914 (Box 9)
  - Papers, 1915-1930 (Box 10)
  - Papers, undated (Box 11)
- Daybooks and Ledgers Series, 1878, 1880-1918
  Please consult with a reference archivist for the locations of these manuscript volumes.